Outro
Who are you people?
Charge!
Kick your asses!
Hold on!
You're supposed to be on our side!
Damn.
What's going on?
Where'd they come from?
Oh, no.
I want your way I
want your
wait to see this answer
It's a matter of fact,
it's not a perfect moment
I've been telling you the story
I've been telling you I'm doing it I'm
only one thing to be I'm gonna lose my
hand I'm gonna lose my hand I'm going
to lose my hand I'm gonna lose my hand
I'm gonna lose my hand
the past, and the past
So gross!
I can't stop now.
Alice!
You must stop. Right now.
Let us handle them.
Stay here and rest a bit.
But I can't.
I just realized who those Red Knights are.
They're not from here.
They're from my world.
That may be.
But they are just a bloodthirsty
mob flailing their swords.
No matter how great their
number, there is nothing to fear.
She's right.
Relax, little lady.
Let us knights take a crack at him.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Truths!
I want a tight formation!
We'll bust through their ranks!
I...
I gotta tell the Emperor.
I have to call this off!
Champion!
We didn't get any orders from the
Emperor about those red bastards, did we?
No, he didn't say anything about him.
Thought so.
Then, if we decided to go
and slaughter them all,
he shouldn't have a problem with that.
I guess not.
We're gonna save our people on
the other side of the canyon.
Soon as the bridge goes up, I want
everyone to charge the other side.
But what bridge? There
ain't no... There will be.
I'll ask someone to make it.
No time to shimmy across a rope.
I'll have to jump across it instead!
Champion!
Goddamn it!
Stop it!
Later, babe!
They're weaker than they look.
He's from the Dark Territory.
No way.
I need your help. For what?
You're the one that made those little
mountains and the canyon behind me, right?
Yeah. All right. Here's the deal.
I need you to make a bridge
across the canyon for my people.
Do that, and my 4,000 pugilists
will cross over and help you fight.
We'll crush these red bastards together.
You'll help?
But you're the enemy.
I do not think this
one is the type to lie.
Hey there.
Okay then.
I'll help your people cross over.
Oh, my God.
They are indifferent, heartless.
Fiends, be gone!
System call!
Discharge!
From the top of that hill, I can
incinerate them all. Make way!
Wait! It's not set!
No! Alice!
Enhance armor!
Bastard, I'm going to kill you for this!
Out of my way or a...
Release the collection!
Commander, go after her.
Thanks, kid. Watch your back.
Don't lose them!
Nice tactics.
Yeah, well, I trained them myself.
Look, they got us hemmed in here,
so South's the only way to go.
We'll have to take them
all on at some point,
but there's so many,
it ain't gonna be easy.
We'll break through the lines
and head South, like you said.
Then put as much distance
between us and them as we can.
As soon as we're far enough away, I'll
try to make another canyon to block them.
I bring a message!
M 'lady Alice has been taken!
Emperor Vector snatched her
up and flew off with her!
The spotter saw his dragon
heading due south! What?
That's where we're...
wait.
He took off with her?
Then when I saw him, he wasn't
just checking out the battle.
Hey, woman!
Your Alice is the Priestess
of Light, ain't she?
The whole point of my people
being here was to catch her.
Why does the Emperor want her so bad?
What'll happen when he gets her?
This world will be destroyed.
That's Vecta's plan.
To take Alice, the Priestess of
Light, down to the world's end altar.
And once there, this world and everything
in it is going to be wiped out.
A dragon cannot fly forever.
And with passengers, they
only last half a day.
Right.
And I guess you should get
going while the getting's good.
You'd let us go?
Just like that.
But you're from the Dark
Territory and he's your emperor.
You're talking treason.
I don't know about that.
At the start of this, Vecta gave
his Council of Ten an order.
That all he wanted was this
priestess of light and now that he's
got what he wanted I'd say his
order to us has been fulfilled,
wouldn't you?
Me and my people are
free to do whatever now,
so if he wanted to help you
and the human army steal the
priestess back from the Emperor
we could a choice is up to us,
right?
We can't disobey the
Emperor if he tells us we
have to fight you then
my people have to obey
or you'll kill us.
But here's what we can do for you we'll
keep the red guys busy
here while you and the
human army catch up to
the Emperor when you
do you tell him what
bastard we're through.
You dyin' for nothin', you tell
him we ain't his pulpits no more!
Now we're talkin'.
That's it, people!
Keep that line open, ya hear?
There's your exit, but
you better hurry up.
We can't hold it forever.
Thank you.
I think I will stay here with him.
Alright then, good luck and stay safe.
You sure about this, woman? Stop it.
You know my name.
You sure about this, Sheyta?
Because there's no guarantee
you'll survive this.
I cannot let anyone else slash you.
Only I reserve the right to. Ha!
Says you.
Come on!
Show me some fire, pugilists!
Get in the circle!
Defend position!
If any of them tries to attack,
wind up and give them hell!
Ready to kick some ass, champion?
Yeah!
Morning, sunshine.
You were out for a while there.
Say something so I know
your brain didn't get fried.
Asshole.
Ah, damn it.
I died.
I fell down some bottomless pit.
Ooh, that sounds both
horrible and pathetic.
You know, you've been
out for eight hours now.
Wait, eight hours?
Why do you look so panicked, man?
Everything's cool.
Right before you got
your ass honed in there,
I dialed the time back
down to one-to-one. What?
Son of a bitch!
What the hell are you messing
around with the time for?
In 12 hours the GSDF is
gonna bust in here and
they'll be gunning for us I
know I've been keeping up.
I cranked the time down because
Captain Miller ordered me to
Using our satellite connection.
I just logged a bunch of players from the
US into the dark territory The hell for
That's a log of you and the caps
movements in there a few minutes ago?
He passed the place you croaked
and is heading due south.
And get this, he's not traveling
with the Dark Territory's army.
He's on his own.
And you know what that means.
You could be chasing after
Alice, or he's got her.
Either way, you should crank up the time.
Nope, not yet.
We have a problem.
Check it out.
That part in red is
what's left of the U .S.
players.
And that black circle half-surrounded by
him is a chunk of the
Dark Territory's army.
Our problem is that white dot that's
the human army or what's left of them
according to the log There's about 700 give
or take if they catch up to the captain.
That would be no bueno
They got to be stopped ASAP then you
better get to it what you got in mind.
I Got us a second batch
of us players on standby
When there's 20 thou I'll drop
them on top of the human army.
That's 28 times their numbers
It's gonna be a friggin' massacre.
Then I'll crank time up
to a thousand to one.
We'll sit back and let
the captain do his thing.
He'll have all the time
in the world and then
some to get Alice to
the southern terminal.
I hope it goes as smooth as you say.
The human side's army is a hell
of a lot tougher than you think.
Hell, those integrity knights
are straight up badasses.
I sat there and watched as they mowed
down the dark territory's front line.
We lost thousands in
one gigantic flash of...
Flash of...
Lightning flash!
It's her!
It totally was!
I'll never forget that, bitch! What?
Who are you talking about?
Guess what, you little four-eyed freak.
I just figured out the Wrath guys in Subcon
are doing the same thing we are. Yeah,
but they got Japanese VR MMO players
logged in and working with the Human Army!
No way!
And I'll bet if Lightning Flash Asuna's in
there, that dual-wielding bastard is too.
This is great.
It's my lucky day.
I'm going back in, baby.
So get me prepped.
Send me to the Human Army's location
with the second batch of players.
Okay, if you want.
But you wasted the only Dark
Knight account we had, remember?
All I got is a basic grunt like
the others, so no complaining.
I ain't using one of those accounts.
I got a special one instead.
Oh, my God.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Oh no, Serenly is going to
barrel through them. Don't!
Oh, my God.
No rapid fire?
Oh, well.
I guess I'm more used to
single-shot weapons anyway.
I'm late. Sorry.
SINONON!
no.
It's your story.
Even though there's no love!
There's no need for love.
My goal.
My goal is just.
Dohka, a Knight mo,
doko ka de, Knight imas yonini?
I'm sorry.
Underworld.